YYeTs.com
人人影视
And -- and did commit the sin of self-pollution.
还有手淫之罪吧
And committed the sin of self-pollution.
还有手淫之罪
10 hard ones.
用力给他十鞭
On this glorious day,
就在今天
Our brave boys muster
我们的勇士集结于此
to face the devil's shock troops...
共同对抗恶魔的先遣部队
French and Indian savages
那些聚集在我们家门口的
massing in the woods right outside our doors.
凶残法国人及印第安野蛮人
And what are you going off to defend?
而你们要保卫的是什么呢
Not Sodom, but Salem.
不是所多玛  而是塞勒姆
We cannot expect god to be on our side
如果我们能容忍这种伤风败俗的人或事
if we tolerate abominations or those who commit them.
上帝还怎么保佑我们
You two will remain in the stocks overnight.
你们俩将被通宵被锁在这里
And you, boy, will bear the mark of your sins
而你小子  将一生背负
the rest of your life.
你罪孽的印记
No, please. Please!
不要啊  求你了
For god's sakes, Sibley.
行行好吧  西布里
The stocks and the lashings are punishment enough.
当众羞辱和鞭刑已经够他受的了
No!
不要啊
Fornicator!
私通者
Judge not...
"你们不要论断人
lest ye be judged.
免得你们被论断"
Who said that?
谁在说话
Jesus. You might have heard of him.
这是耶稣说的  你也许听说过他
John Alden.
约翰·奥登
My respect for your father's memory
别以为有我对你父亲的那点尊重
can only shield you so long.
你就可以在这里肆无忌惮
It's a good thing you're mustering out tonight.
你今晚就要出征了  别在这惹事
Like it or not, Sibley's in charge.
不管你愿不愿意  西布里现在手握重权
He tolerated your father,
他或许能容忍你父亲
but he won't be happy till he sees you swing.
但他可不会容你在这放肆
Didn't you learn anything today?
你今天还没学到教训吗
Yes, yes, if I have to spend one more night
是啊  是啊  如果多给我一个晚上的时间
under the same stars as that bastard George Sibley,
接近乔治·西布里那个王八蛋
I will gut him like the pig that he is.
我会像杀猪样宰了他
If -- talking like that will land you in the stocks.
你说这话会被当众惩罚的
No day soon.
没机会了
I'd rather die fighting the French and the Indians
我宁愿死在战场上
than get pissed on by the good souls of Salem.
也不愿在这被人侮辱
So, you're really leaving.
所以你是真要走了
Mary, trust me.
玛丽  相信我
I will come back for you.
我会回来找你的
Look.
看
This is all that I have.
这是我仅有的了
And I swear on my parents' grave.
我以我父母之灵起誓
This is my vow.
这就是我的誓言
This war will not last a year.
这场战争顶多持续一年
Forward!
前进
Stay in formation, gentlemen.
保持队形  先生们
Isn't but a half-day's ride.
大概就半天的路程
I can't make it.
我做不到
I think I'm gonna be sick again.
我觉得我又要吐了
As soon as you sit down inside, it will settle.
没事儿的  进去坐坐就好了
Wait your betters, girl.
让长者先行  小姑娘
Peace be upon you.
愿上帝保佑你
And upon you.
你也是
Though there are things to be said for war.
虽然战争无情
Gives a certain kind of man someplace to end up
但对某些人来说  战死沙场
other than the end of a brand...
远比被处以极刑
or a rope.
更有意义
You'll thank me one day.
终有一天你会感谢我的
Stay strong.
坚强点
After tonight, it will all be over.
今晚之后  一切都将结束
Tituba, wait.
缇图芭  等等
I've changed my mind. I want to go back.
我改变主意了  我想回去
There is no place for that child in Salem.
塞勒姆没有那孩子的容身之地
George Sibley drove John Alden off to die in the war.
乔治·西布里让约翰·奥登战死沙场
What do you think he's gonna do to you
你觉得他要是发现了你怀着约翰的孩子
when he finds out you're pregnant with John's baby?
他会怎么对你
Do not fear the woods.
不要害怕森林
The woods are gonna take care of that little soul...
森林会照顾好那个小小的灵魂的
and you.
还有你
What is this place?
这是什么地方
You want to live? Lie still.
你若还想活  就好好躺着
Please.
求求你
It's all that I have left of him.
他留给我的只有这个孩子了
Hush.
别出声
No, wait. I-I-I don't want to do this.
不  等等  我不想这么做
You don't have a choice, Mary.
你别无选择  玛丽
Please.
求求你
- This is what you want. - Please.
-这才是你想要的  -拜托
This is what you want.
这才是你想要的
- No...please. - Let him in.
-不  求你了  -让他进去
No, please.
不要啊  拜托
Stay there!
别过来
John. John. John, help me.
约翰  约翰  约翰  救救我
Help me!
救我
Now tell him.
快告诉他
Say it. This is what you want.
说吧  说这是你想要的
Yes. Yes!
是  是
Yes!
是我想要的
All the world shall be yours in return.
为了弥补你  整个世界都将是你的
All the world.
整个世界
...from heaven in flaming fire,
...来自天堂的熊熊烈火
taking vengeance upon all those who know not God,
将向不信奉上帝之人寻仇
who have disobeyed the gospel! Read for yourself the truth.
向违背教义之人寻仇  自己来看清真理吧
The terrible truth --
可怕的真理
Witches among us, the devil in Salem.
我们中有巫师  塞勒姆有恶魔
For you, sir.
给您  先生
No.
不用
Easy. Easy.
慢点  慢点
This is the Alden house,
这里是奥登家
and there ain't any Aldens left.
奥登家的人已经都死光了
So you are either a ghost, or you're about to be one.
所以你要么是鬼魂  要么就要成为鬼魂了
That's a harsh way to say "Welcome home."
这样欢迎别人回家可不是待客之道啊
Johnny?
约翰
Can't be.
怎么可能
I heard you was dead -- killed in the war.
我听说你死了啊  战死了
I wished I was a couple of times.
我倒是希望死了
Ah, well, they can't keep a good man down.
好人是不会轻易就死了的
Saw three men strung up on the way into town
我在来的路上看到三个人被绞死示众
and a new gallows being built in the heart of the common.
公共集会地中间还建了一个新绞刑架
What the hell is that?
这是怎么回事
Precious Salem caught up in a stinking witch panic.
我们的塞勒姆因为巫师的事人心惶惶
Witch panic?
巫师
Who did the bigwigs send in to put out the fire,
有权有势的那些人又派谁去平息了
the Almighty increase Mather?
那个对上帝深信不疑的麦哲吗
No, his son -- Cotton.
不  是他儿子柯顿
And not a chip off the old block -- barely a splinter.
只可惜他比起父亲差远了  就是个废物
I remember when we were kids
我记得我们小时候
he used to dress like a girl.
他就穿得跟个姑娘似的
Fought like one, too.
打起架来也扭扭捏捏
Well, he's all growed-up now.
他现在长大了
A fine fool in fine silk clothes,
长成了满身缠着绫罗绸缎的傻子
and not just any fool, the most dangerous kind --
但不是普通的傻子  而是最危险的那种
the kind that thinks he knows everything.
自以为无所不知
But you didn't come back for all this horseshit.
你回来不是为了听这些屁话的吧
You come back for one thing and one thing only.
你回来的目的只有一个
Truth told, she's finer than ever.
说实话  她现在过得很好
And she's the richest woman in Salem.
她是塞勒姆最富有的女人
And why not?
为什么呢
She's mary Sibley now.
因为她现在是西布里的妻子
Sibley?
西布里
George Sibley.
乔治·西布里
But his wife --
但他妻子...
Died a few years ago.
几年前去世了
You've been gone a long time, John.
你离开太长时间了  约翰
Keep your powder in your bag.
时刻做好准备吧
One day,
有一天
your Mary will be the richest widow in the country.
你的玛丽会成为我们国家最富有的寡妇
The driver's at the door
司机来了
with some packages for you, ma'am.
带来了您的包裹  夫人
Send him in.
让他进来
And, Nathaniel, take Mr. Sibley with you.
纳撒尼尔  带西布里先生一起走吧
Time for his bath.
到洗澡时间了
Now, Isaac, tell me some news of the world.
艾萨克  现在告诉我都有哪些新闻吧
Saw a dusty fella walking into town today.
今天看到一个人风尘仆仆地进城了
I couldn't believe my eyes.
我简直不敢相信自己的眼睛
Why?
为什么
It was John Alden.
那个人是约翰·奥登
Welcome back, Reverend Mather.
欢迎回来  麦哲牧师
Rum, gin, ale?
朗姆酒   杜松子酒和麦芽酒
Yes.
好
I need three strong men.
我需要三个身强体壮的人
I can pay.
我会付钱的
For what?
干什么
To subdue a girl.
去制服一个姑娘
Reverend Lewis.
路易丝牧师
Please help my daughter.
求你帮帮我女儿
And be careful.
注意安全
Tie her down!
绑住她
Please, I beg you, sir. Please, make this stop.
求你了  牧师  求你了  救救我
I can do nothing, Mercy, unless you tell me...
梅西  我也无能为力  除非你告诉我
Who is it torments you?
是谁在折磨你
S-she's right there.
她就在那里
"She"?
她
Who is here?
谁在这里
Mercy, you must tell me!
梅西  你必须告诉我
Who is in this room with us?!
这里还有谁
The hag! The old woman!
那个女巫  那个老太婆
She's standing right there!
她就站在那里
Please.
求你了
A simple physic.
这是药
To sleep.
帮你入睡
Please. Please.
求你了  求你了
We call it a spectral attack --
我们称之为魔鬼侵袭...
The work of witches.
是女巫所为
Pray for her.
为她祈祷吧
I call bullshit.
一派胡言
She's clearly touched in the head.
她显然是精神失常了
She needs a doctor, not your prayers.
她需要医生  不是祷告
Don't dawdle, child.
别磨蹭  孩子
I want you in the front row
我要你坐到前排
Where Cotton Mather can't help but be dazzled by your charms.
柯顿·麦哲定会为你的魅力而倾倒
For heaven's sake, mother,
看在上帝的份上  母亲
why not just wrap me in silk and parade me on the auction block?
干脆把我裹进丝绸  放到拍卖会上好了
Fear no man's war.
人类的战争不足为惧
For only a war from hell could destroy Salem.
只有来自地狱的战火能摧毁塞勒姆
The devil was never going to let
决不能让魔鬼
a promised land be built here
不费一兵一卒
without a fight, without a battle!
就攻占这里
And witches armed with deadly malice
巫师所拥有致命的恶意
are the most malignant and insidious weapons
便是最为狠毒而阴险的武器
in that battle,
在这场战役
in that war.
这场战争中
Even a single witch in Salem is enough to destroy
只要塞勒姆有一个巫师  便足以毁灭
everything we have built and ever hope to build here!
我们所建立的一切  和我们所有的远大愿景
Now, we have already killed three of them,
如今  我们已经处决了三名巫师
and yet their malice continues unabated.
但他们的恶意仍未消逝
Why?
为什么
Because there are still witches here among us!
因为我们之中仍有巫师存在
Perhaps in this very hall!
或许就在这座大厅里
Imagine a foe you can't see armed with weapons unknown
设想这些在暗处的敌人  拥有未知的武器和巫术
and the ability to appear as any one of us!
看上去却和常人别无二致
Then how can you hope to identify the correct culprit?
既然如此  你希望谁来指认罪犯
Have you seen the girl, sir?
你见过那个女孩了吗  先生
Even now, Mercy Lewis bleeds from 100 wounds --
即使现在  梅西·路易丝遍体鳞伤
some impossible to self-inflict.
这些伤绝不会是自残所致
She is the one who will tell us who does this.
她将向我们指认犯罪之人
I see.
我明白了
The ravings of a poor, sick girl
重病缠身的可怜女孩  她的疯言疯语
will help you identify what your reason fails to deliver.
就能解释你这说不清的逻辑了吗
My father --
我父亲
Yes, of course. Your father.
是  没错  你父亲
Did your father, whom we all so respect,
备受大家尊崇的  你的父亲
offer you any advice when he sent you in his stead
让你代替他过来帮忙的时候
to our aid?
提供什么建议了吗
He...advised caution.
他给出了警告
Caution?
警告
And are we to take three people hung
因为小麦哲的警告
as the measure of Mather Junior's caution?
我们就要将三人绞死吗
There could be nothing worse for Salem,
在塞勒姆  甚至在全国
for the country, than a witch hunt.
没有比巫师追捕行动更可怕的事了
Witches.
巫师
Indeed.
正是
As my beloved husband, the head of your selectmen, reminds me,
正如我亲爱的丈夫  你们的执行官所言
there is something worse than a witch hunt --
还有比巫师追捕行动更可怕的东西
a witch.
那就是巫师
A witch?
巫师
Sure, that's bad.
那一定很可怕
But why not an ogre...
为什么不是食人魔
or a goblin?
或是哥布林
Why not a dragon, long as we're talking about fairy tales?
既然要说神话生物  为什么不能是龙
John Alden.
约翰·奥登
We all welcome captain alden home from his long,
感谢你多年来对我们的英勇守护
long service in our defense.
欢迎回家  奥登上尉
Puritans know their sun is setting.
清教徒自知势力衰减
Nothing like a new enemy or a new old enemy
没什么比新的敌人  或者新的老对手
to get people behind you.
更能笼络人心了
Captain Alden.
奥登上尉
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Mr. Sibley and I are hosting a small dinner tomorrow night.
西布里先生和我明晚会举办小型晚宴
We'd be honored if you'd join.
你的到来将使舍下蓬荜生辉
Why are you staring at me?
为什么盯着我
I don't even know you.
我甚至不认识你
Isaac?
艾萨克
Isaac the fornicator.
私通者艾萨克
Hide your wives.
藏好你的妻子
Hide your daughters. Hell, your sheep!
你的女儿  连羊都得小心点
All right, look.
好吧
So, what do you want from me?
你想要我怎么做
Listen to me, John Alden.
听我说  约翰·奥登
Coming home to Salem to get out of the war
离开战场回到塞勒姆
is like jumping in the ocean to get out of the rain.
就好比穿越刀山  又跳入火海
Truth hides.
真相秘而不宣
They could be anyone.
谁都可能会是他们
Oh, they who? Who's they?
拜托  他们  他们是谁
Witches!
巫师
Ain't no fairy tale.
不是神话传说
They're real.
巫师是真实存在的
All these years,
这些年来
your Mary's the only one who's ever done me a good turn.
你的玛丽是唯一向我施以援手的人
She's not my Mary now.
她不再是我的玛丽了
You left once before.
你已经离开过一次了
Look what happened.
看看都发生了些什么
Don't walk out on us again.
不要再抛下我们了
Is this really necessary?
真的有必要如此吗
A witches' familiars --
巫师的亲信
demons, usually in the form of an animal.
魔鬼  常以动物之形存在
Cat, rat, a bird, or a toad --
猫  鼠  鸟  或者蟾蜍
they perform all sorts of useful tasks
它们只要填饱肚子
as long as they're fed.
就能执行各种任务
You heard what she told us.
你也听到她说的话了
She was forced to feed their familiars.
她被迫喂养他们的亲信
She must be searched for the marks --
因此她身上一定有标志
teats where she suckled them.
那些它们用以吮吸的裂口
Please help her.
请帮帮她
"Woe to the inhabitants of the earth and of the sea!
"可是地与海的居民有祸了
"For the devil has come down unto you with great wrath
因为魔鬼知道自己的时日无多
because he knoweth that he hath but a short time."
就怀着烈怒下到你们那里去了"
Revelations chapter 12:12.
《启示录》12章12节
I see the end of the world
看得出世界末日
urges you onto greater efforts.
让你更卖力了
Mm, as it must us all.
它敦促着我们每个人
Our granny used to scare us silly
我的祖母以前总喜欢
with those witch stories.
用女巫的故事吓唬我们
But she'd really terrify my brothers.
不过她真的吓到我兄弟们了
She told them witches could steal a man's --
她说女巫能偷走男人的
Would you like that, Gloriana,
你喜欢这样吗  格里安娜
without the bother of the man attached?
不必受到任何男人的束缚
Not this man.
你不同
My darling.
亲爱的
See you next time, governor.
下次见  长官
Just attending to the poor.
我只是来关照穷苦人民
No doubt -- and the poor in spirit.
毫无疑问  精神匮乏的穷人
Captain alden, right?
奥登上尉是吗
I haven't seen you since we were children.
孩提之后我就没有见过你
I expected to see you up at Harvard.
本来期待能在哈佛见到你
Surprised to hear that you'd run off to join the militia --
没想到你却加入了民兵团
like a servant.
像那些仆人一样
I would have loved to spend four years
我很乐意花上四年
counting angels on the heads of pins, but...
去数数针头上有多少天使  不过
...there was a war on.
战争当前
Pity.
真是可惜
I owe everything to my education.
学习让我受益匪浅
Taught you everything about hunting witches?
学校教你怎么追捕巫师了吗
No.
没有
But my father burnt scores back in Essex,
不过我父亲在艾塞克斯时便对此颇有研究
and I've read every book there is on the subject --
而且我读过与之相关的一切书籍
in eight languages.
八种语言的
So, you learned your hunting from books.
那你就是从书上学会怎么捉巫师了
Well, that's a bit like learning the facts of life
就像是从你未经世事的小姨那里
from your maiden aunt.
学习生活真相
But never mind.
但也无所谓了
You're here now,
你刚好在这
and you're the expert on witches,
又是巫师专家
So let me ask you.
让我问问你
What do these awful witches want, huh?
那些可怕的巫师想要什么
The same thing we all want...
与我们渴望的一样
...a country of their own.
一个属于自己的国家
And here I've been wasting my time fighting mere Indians.
我却在这浪费时间攻打区区印第安人
Good night, Harvard.
晚安  高材生
Time for your feeding.
喂食时间到了
Yes.
很好
Someone, help me!
来人啊  帮帮我
Help me.
救命
Yes.
很好
No.
不要
Help me! Help!
救我 救我
Help!
救命
George, don't fight it.
乔治  别挣扎
You know it only hurts more.
那只会让你更痛苦
You took away everything I had, George Sibley...
你夺走了我的一切  乔治·西布里
everything I loved.
我深爱的一切
Can you imagine how good it feels
你知道这种感觉多美妙吗
to take everything you have,
夺走你的所有
destroy all you've built,
摧毁你建立的一切
and devour your very soul?
并亲手毁灭你的灵魂
All done.
好了
I would like to make a toast to our hostess,
我想敬我们的女主人
Mary sibley,
玛丽·西布里
who has shown us that true piety and true beauty
她向我们展示了真正的虔诚和美丽
amount to the same worship.
同样值得赞颂
Indeed.
没错
Beauty is the last miracle allowed in an ugly...
美丽是丑陋堕落的世界上
fallen world.
最后一个奇迹
Magistrate Hale and I are concerned
霍尔法官和我
about our daughter's inner beauty, Reverend Mather.
为我们女儿的内在美而担忧  麦哲牧师
Perhaps you could suggest a tutor for her,
或许你可以为她推荐一个导师
a Harvard man -- like yourself?
一个哈佛毕业生  向您本人这样的
I believe there is only so much you can learn from books.
我觉得书上能学到的东西有限
Experience is our true teacher.
经验才是真正的老师
Don't you agree, captain Alden?
你同意吗  奥登上尉
Well, that depends on the experience.
这取决于那些经验是什么了
Yours must have been fascinating -- with the indians.
你的经验一定非常吸引人  那些印第安人
They're so mysterious,
他们如此神秘
So...natural.
如此接近自然
Natural?
自然
"Unnatural," I'd say.
要我说是反常
Soulless savages.
没有灵魂的野蛮人
I assure you, ma'am, the indians do have souls,
相信我  夫人  印第安人有灵魂
if any of us do.
如果我们有的话
"If"?
"如果"
And what about witches?
那巫师呢
Do they have souls, too?
他们也有灵魂吗
They do.
他们有
But they have deeded them to the devil himself
但他们将自己的灵魂出卖给了魔鬼
in exchange for powers and all that they desire.
以换取权力和他们渴望的一切事物
- A contract? - Indeed.
-魔鬼协议吗  -没错
Ironic.
真是讽刺
As I believe, by law,
我相信在法律中
a woman's not allowed to enter a contract
女性只有通过丈夫
but through the agency of their husband.
才能与别人签订合同
Nathaniel.
纳撒尼尔
Yes, ma'am.
好的  夫人
Not all witches are women.
并不是所有的巫师都是女巫
And what do you think, captain Alden?
你认为呢  奥登上尉
I don't know.
我不知道
I think some things just beggar belief,
我认为有些事情还是得眼见为实
like an honest frenchman or a faithful woman,
就像是诚实的法国人  或是忠诚的女人
things that I'll believe in if and when I see one.
这些我只有亲眼见到了才会相信
I find I worry more
我发现比起巫师
about the french and the indian attacks
我还是更担心法国人和
than I do witches.
印第安人的入侵
What's your opinion, captain Alden?
你怎么看  奥登上尉
Just how vulnerable are we?
我们的防守如何
Are you all right, captain Alden?
你还好吗  奥登上尉
I think this rich food doesn't agree with me.
可能这些丰盛的食物我还是不太习惯
Some fresh air might help.
呼吸一下新鲜空气或许能有所帮助
I was told you were killed.
有人跟我说你死了
Was that before or after you married Sibley?
那是在你嫁给西布里之前还是之后
I remember being told once
我记得有人对我说过
that the war wouldn't last a year.
战争不会超过一年
That wasn't up to me.
这不是我能决定的
I waited for you.
我一直在等着你
Years and years without a word.
年复一年  你却杳无音讯
I couldn't write.
我没法写信
No, of course not.
当然了
Too busy saving the country.
忙于拯救国家
Not exactly.
不是的
I was captured.
我被俘虏了
Their priest man told the others not to take this away from me.
他们的神父对其他人说不要夺走这个
He said the universe itself was made out of vows,
他说宇宙由誓言所构成
and breaking them carries consequences.
破坏誓言会带来严重后果
I know that this is just half a silver coin,
我知道这只是半枚银币
and you have... no shortage of silver now.
如今  你的金银珠宝享之不尽
Mary, come with me.
玛丽  跟我走吧
Now...tonight.
现在  今晚
I have money in a bank in new york.
我在纽约的银行有一些积蓄
It's different there.
那里很不一样
There's not a puritan in sight.
你不会见到一个清教徒
It's not too late.
现在还来得及
We can be together
我们能在一起
anywhere.
无论何地
Anywhere but here.
除了这里
New York?
纽约
Yeah.
对
Is that before or after you were captured?
那是在你被俘虏之前还是之后
You walk out of here one night,
那个晚上你离开了这里
and you come back years later.
这么多年后你才回来
A-and you think that --
你以为我...
Mary.
玛丽
Come here.
过来
No.
不
I can't.
我不能
It's impossible.
不可能了
He'd never let me.
他不会允许
Now, now, Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Even you have no right to monopolize a guest
就算是您也不能独占咱们的贵客
as fascinating as Captain Alden,
我们的奥登上尉
for whom I have a rare gift,
我可是有珍贵的礼物要送你
a cigar of tobacco from Guyana with some Brandy.
咱们来点圭亚那的雪茄和白兰地如何
I'm afraid all this...
恐怕这一切
civilized eating and drinking has laid me out, magistrate.
文明的吃饭喝酒的方式让我不适  长官
You told me he was dead!
你告诉我他死了
It's not like counting sheep, honey.
预言从不会如此精确  亲爱的
more like counting shadows.
总会有模糊的盲点
But it don't change a thing.
但这都无关紧要
What's John Alden compared to all that lies before you?
约翰·奥登比起你眼前的一切算得了什么
Stop your weeping, woman.
别哭了  女人
That boy don't deserve those tears.
那个人不配得到你的眼泪
They're not for him.
不是为他而流
They're for the girl I once was.
是为了我曾经的少女心
That girl belongs to somebody else now.
你早已回不去了
Was it he that left you to the wolves?
是他把你留给了一群狼吗
No, child.
不是的  孩子
It was he that saved you from the wolves
是他从狼群中把你救出
and raised you up to all of this.
造就成今日的你
You have a grand vision.
你有更伟大的目标
Don't lose sight of it.
不要忘记
Tomorrow, the moon is with us.
明天  月亮将与我们同在
Tomorrow, it begins.
明天  序幕拉开
Leave your anger and your pain for the kenaima to feed on.
将你所有的愤怒和痛苦交给卡耐马恶鬼吞噬
Has he not been true to his vow?
他违背过自己的誓言吗
Are not your enemies now your slaves?
如今  你的敌人都已成为你的奴隶
Do you not have everything that you desire --
难道你不是拥有了渴望的一切
Wealth, power?
财富  权力
Almost everything.
几乎一切
Pardon me, ma'am. A gentleman to see you.
抱歉  夫人  有人求见
Mr. Corey.
科里先生
To what do I owe the pleasure?
阁下有何贵干
I was wondering if I might talk to you, ma'am.
我在想是不是应该和你谈谈  夫人
I had a small farm.
我有过一个小农场
First, it broke my heart.
它先是伤了我的心
then it broke my back.
然后伤了我的后背
As you and I both know, the heart heals.
你我都知道  心会痊愈
The back never does.
背伤却永远不会
I took up trapping.
从此我开始靠设陷阱捕猎为生
It's a meager living -- ruined the Indians.
这种拮据的生活当初毁了印第安人
Now it's ruining me.
现在正在逐渐毁掉我
Thing about trapping is you get your good catch at night.
设陷阱的时候  猎物通常都在夜里踏入陷阱
But by morning, it's someone else's meal.
可到了早上  却通常成了别人的食物
Me, I stay with my traps.
至于我  我会守着我的陷阱
Fascinating, Mr. Corey, but --
很精彩  科里先生  但是
That's why I was there...
这就是为什么我来到这
The night you did it...
我知道那天晚上
You and your cinnamon girl.
你和你的仆人都干了些什么
You waited a long time.
你等了很久才来找我啊
Nobody's business till now.
因为之前不涉及到任何人
But that was John Alden's baby that you buried out there.
但那个被你烧掉的孩子是约翰·奥登的
And the way he feels about you, he has a right to know.
他为你如此着迷  他有权知道真相
So, are you gonna tell him?
所以该由你来说呢
Or am I?
还是我来
Oh, blast this wretched thing.
该死的
That's not bad.
画得很不错
Reverend Lewis says drawing is idolatry,
路易斯牧师说绘画是邪神崇拜
like worshiping nature or something.
如同崇拜自然或者什么
Well, there might be worse things to worship.
总比崇拜些更糟糕的东西好
I'd like to draw you sometime.
有机会的话  我想为你画像
I'm not sure I'd like to see a portrait of me.
我可不确定是否想看到画中的自己
Besides, I have no time to sit.
再说了  我也没有时间
I'm on way out of town.
我要离开了
So soon?
这么快
Afraid of witches...
是因为害怕巫师吗
or being taken for one?
还是怕被当成是巫师
It's a long way to New York.
纽约离这可有一段路程
Good day.
祝你有愉快的一天
Oh, I didn't mean to frighten you.
我不是故意吓你的
Oh, I'm not frightened.
我没被吓到
Just surprised.
只是感到意外
Yes, of course --
那是当然
A girl brave enough to sketch in a graveyard.
对一个敢独自在墓地里素描的女孩这算什么
I'm not afraid of the dead,
我不害怕死人
nor the living for that matter.
活人也不怕
That's because you know nothing of death
那是因为你对死亡一无所知
And less of life.
对生命更加的无知
I could teach you --
我可以教给你
about life...
关于生命
and death...
和死亡
and many things in between.
还有二者之间的东西
Do you know what killed nearly every woman buried here?
你知道几乎每个埋在这的女人都死于什么
Love.
爱情
Most died in childbirth.
大多数都死于分娩
So, love is to a woman what war is to a man --
所以说爱情之于女人就好比战争之于男人
the most deadly thing they'll do.
都是所能做的最致命的事情
Only a fool runs quickly to war or love.
只有傻子才会迫不及待的奔向战争和爱情
You'd best watch yourself.
你自己小心为妙
Thank you...Mrs. Sibley.
谢谢您  西布里夫人
I can only aspire to your happy wisdom.
对于您的智慧我真是望尘莫及
Where do the witches meet?
巫师们在哪里见面
In the woods.
树林里
How many?
有多少人
I don't know.
我不知道
Who are they?
他们是谁
I --
我
I can't see their faces.
我看不到他她们的脸
Like there's these heads of animals
好像是一些动物的头颅
like a stag and a pig and a wolf.
一头牡鹿  一头猪和一只狼
But you know who they are?
可你还是知道他们是谁
Yes.
是的
Their names.
他们的名字
Why won't you tell me their names?
为什么你不告诉我他们的名字
She won't let me.
她不允许我
"She"?
她
- Yes. - Who?
-是的  -谁
Who is she?
她是谁
Tell me.
告诉我
- I can't. - Tell me the names!
-我不能  -把名字告诉我
My god, Mercy.
天哪  梅西
Though she cannot speak a name,
尽管她不能说出名字
she will show us the witch.
她会指出女巫是谁
Oh, no!
天呐  不要
Sorry, Captain.
抱歉  上尉
You can't leave Salem just yet.
你现在不能离开塞勒姆
Something you've got to see.
有些东西你得看看
Is this him, the witch?
是他吗  那个巫师
I think so.
我想是吧
All the books say if the victim --
所有的书籍上都说如果受害者
Never mind your books.
别管的你书怎么说
Is this the witch?
他是不是巫师
He won't plead either way.
他不愿开口  既不承认也不否认
Is that so?
这样吗
Won't dignify the accusation.
本来也不是什么真正的指控
If you can call a young girl's
一个小女孩朝着你吐口水
spit an accusation.
这也能算是指控吗
What I have to say,
要我开口的话
I'll say to Captain John Alden.
我要跟约翰·奥登上尉谈
You just find me Captain Alden.
只要你把奥登上尉找来
I'll have plenty to say.
我可是有不少话要讲呢
I have sent men for captain Alden,
我已经派人找过奥登上尉
but I'm told he's left town.
但是我被告知他已经离开了
Just obtain a plea.
想办法让他招供
And if he remains silent?
如果他还是不肯说呢
You've been granted power.
大家赋予了你权力
Use it. Press him for an answer.
好好利用它  从他嘴里逼出答案
Let the same devil that holds his tongue
看看令他守口如瓶的恶魔是否
hold the stones.
经得起巨石的碾压
Hurry. The sabbath is about to begin.
快点  集会马上就要开始了
One, two, three, and four.
一  二  三 四
Raise the devil to our door.
魔鬼  听吾之召唤
Call the pig, the wolf, the ram.
众生之灵  猪  狼  羊
Come to the circle, all who can.
应吾之召  众灵重现
Make him walk on floor to roof.
他将再次行走于这片土地
Drink to him with horn and hoof.
我们将与他举杯共饮
One, two, three, and four.
一  二  三  四
The devil is here.
魔鬼已至
Now sleep no more.
别再沉睡
And all the world shall be yours in return.
世间万物将尽在你掌握
If your witches meet here,
如果你说的巫师们在这集会
they got better night eyes than I do.
那他们夜视一定不错
They don't need night eyes.
他们根本不需要视力
The night is their eyes.
夜晚就是他们的眼睛
What the hell is this?
这都是什么鬼东西
Gifts to the devil himself --
给恶魔的献祭
The unborn.
都是未出生的婴儿
Cruor innocentia.
无辜者之血
Maleficarum. Pestilentia.
巫师  瘟疫
Walpurgisnacht.
五朔节之夜
Consummatum est.
仪式已完成
Now it begins.
一切即将开始
The circle was broken.
祭祀圈被破坏了
By who?
被谁
Satan!
撒旦
Please, sir.
我请求你  先生
I don't want to to do this.
我也不愿这么做
Then don't.
那就别这么做
Be reasonable, man.
讲讲道理吧
I have the power to press you for an answer.
我有合法的权力对你进行逼供
All you have to do is say the words "Guilty"
只要你开口  承认自己有罪
or "Not guilty,"
或是无罪
And we can stop all of this.
我们就能停止这一切
If I say "Guilty," you'll hang me before dawn.
如果我承认有罪  黎明之前我就会被绞死
And if I say not,
如果我坚持自己无罪
my fate is still in the hands of you bastards.
我的命运仍将握在你们这群混蛋手中
I'll hold my peace and trust in the Lord.
所以我宁愿沉默  将命运交给上帝
Lower the stones!
把石头放下来
I ask you again.
我再问你一次
Are you guilty...
你承认自己有罪
or not?
或是无罪
We're dead.
我们死定了
No, we are not.
不会的
Good as.
离死期也不远了
I thought you've seen them before.
这一切你不是早就见识过吗
You wanted me to see them, and I saw them.
你想让我看到这些  我也确实看到了
And they saw us.
可他们也看见了我们
And I told you they could be anybody.
我跟你说过  他们可能是任何人
Okay, just...
好吧
calm down.
冷静点
Have you something to say?
你有什么话要说吗
More stones.
再加点石头吧
Giles!
吉尔斯
Get the hell off of him!
都给我离他远点
Alden!
奥登
He's dead!
他死了
"Woe to the inhabitants...
"地与海的居民
"of the earth and of the sea.
你们有祸了
For the devil has come down unto you."
因为魔鬼即将降临"
Son of a bitch. Son of a...
你这个狗娘养的
No! No!
不
Get!
放手
My father's boots were the very first in Salem.
我父亲是最早踏上塞勒姆这片土地的人
And I'm warning every goddamn one of you murdering,
我警告你们这里每一个杀人如麻
hypocritical puritan bastards
虚假伪善的清教徒混蛋
that these boots will be the last!
你们都不会有好下场
I will ask you once again.
我再问你一次
Who was there?
谁在那里
Who saw us?
谁看见了我们
I will tell you again.
我也再回答你一次
I do not know.
我不知道
It is difficult to see past a muzzle flash.
当时枪口的火焰太亮了  很难看清
Then I suggest you find out, Mr. Hale.
那我建议你尽快查清楚  霍尔先生
There's no turning back.
现在已经没法回头了
The witch hunt has begun,
巫师追捕行动已经开始
and we will be running the trials.
而主持审判的会是我们
You understand that, don't you, George?
你明白吧  乔治  不是吗
You best of all.
你应该最清楚
We will use the trials
我们会利用审判
to turn the puritans against each other.
让那些清教徒自相残杀
They will hunt and kill
他们将会追捕  屠杀
and drown in their very own blood
最终淹没于自己的鲜血当中
till there's no puritans left standing...
直到再无一名清教徒生还
And Salem...
而塞勒姆
is ours.
将属于我们